Guide to the Andrews Memorial Bookplate Collection of Irene D. Andrews Pace (School and College Bookplates)
Yale University Arts Library
- Bookplates
  - D – K (Box 2, Folder 8-17)
    - Funck Professional School, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Mlle. Latesse, artist
    - Gand University, Belgium, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      R. de Cramer, artist
    - George Washington University, Washington, DC, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - George Washington University, Washington, DC, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      C. K. Berryman, artist
    - Georgia School of Technology, Atlanta, GA, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Georgetown College, Washington, DC, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Geneseo Normal Library, Teachers College, NY, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - German Theological School, Newark, NJ, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Gewerbeschule Ellwangen, Germany, 1925; 3 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Ed.Wengert, artist
    - Girard College Library, Girard College, PA, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Girls School of Wessel, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      H. Nernst des of Harzburg, artist
    - Girton College, University of Cambridge, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Harry Soane, artist
    - Gladstone Memorial, 1901 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      T. E. H., artist
    - Glasgow Church Institute, Glasgow, Scotland, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Glasgow College, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Swan, artist
    - Gonville and Caius College, University of Cambridge, UK, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Gordon College of Theology, Wenham, MA, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      E. K., artist
    - Gothmund Evangelische Kinderheim, Germany, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Werner Evers, artist
    - Goucher College, Baltimore, MD, undated; 7 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Goucher College, Baltimore, MD, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Hans Schuler, artist
    - Goucher College Library, Baltimore, MD, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      T. Woodhead, artist
    - Green Mountain Junior College Library, Poultney, VT, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Green Row Academy, Abby Holm, Cumberland, England, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Gresham College, Holborn, London, England, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      J. Perkins, artist
    - Grey Coat Hospital, Westminster, London, England, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Grove House Academy, St. Peters, Margate, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Gustavus Adolphus College, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Gymnasium Celeanum Zwolle, Netherlands, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Dora Geldzalder, artist
    - Hailebury College, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Hallamshire College, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Hamilton College Library, Clinton, NY, undated; 5 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      M. L.Sanford, artist
    - Hamline University Library, Saint Paul, MN, undated; 9; bookplate (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Hampton Institute, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Harrow School, Middlesex, England, UK, undated; 15 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Harvard College Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, undated; 48 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Harvard College Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, undated; 4 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      J. D. Leland & Co, artist; F. C. Blank, artist
    - Harvard College Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
      B.H.W., artist
    - Harvard College Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Sidney Waugh, artist
    - Harvard College Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Grassby, artist
    - Harvard College Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Elihu Vedder, artist
    - Harvard College Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Rogers and La Rose, artists
    - Harvard College Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, undated; 17 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Bruce Rogers, artist
    - Harvard College Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, undated; 3 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Andrew Filner, artist
    - Harvard College Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Hapgood, artist
    - Harvard College Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Harald Jensen (of Denmark), artist
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, undated; 31 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      E. H. G., artist
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, 1850 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Harvard University Library, Cambridge, MA, 1900 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      B. G. Goodhue, artist
    - Harvard Law Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, undated; 3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Haverford College, Haverford, PA, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Hele's School, University of Exeter, Exeter, England, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Townsend, artist
    - Helmsburg High School, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Highgate School, London, England, UK, undated; 3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Highgate Literary and Scientific Inst., 1913; 3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Historicky Seminar Komenskeho University v Bratislave, Slovakia, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Vladimir Pukl, artist
    - Hobart College Library, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Holy Cross College, Worcester, MA, undated; 4 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Honolulu Academy of Arts Library, 1930; 3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Valentine Angelo (of San Francisco), artist
    - Hopkins School, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Frederick Lester Sexton, artist
    - Hotchkiss School, Lakeville, CT, undate; 2 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Hughes High School, Cincinnati, OH, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Elmer Porter, artist
    - Hutchins School, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Indiana State Teachers College, undated; 1; note (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Institute of 1770, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Institute of Paper Chemistry, Appleton, WI, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Institute of the B. V. Mary York, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
      G. Goldie, inv. & del.; Hooper, sc.
    - Instituto Camara Pestana, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Instituto Feinaigliano, Dublin, Ireland, undated; 3 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Sandys, artist
    - Instituto Ibero Americano, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
      M. B. (of Puerto Rico), artist
    - Instituto Ibero Americano, Valencia, Spain, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
      E. Furio, artist
    - Instituto Portogues De Oncologia, Portugal, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Int'l Y. M. C. A. Training School, Springfield, MA, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Ivrea Liceo Ginnasio Botta, Ivrea, Italy, 1930; 2 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      F. Corandini, artist
    - James Millikin University, Illinois, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - J. B. Kidd's Drawing Academy, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Jena Public Trade School, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
      G. Klieman (of Jena), artist
    - Jesus College Cambridge, University of Cambridge, undated; 7 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - John B Stetson University, Deland, FL, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - John Elbridge Hudson, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - John Hopkins University, Baltimore, MD, undated; 12 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Kaiser Franz Joseph Gymnasium Ostrava, Czech Republic, 1901 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Holtmans, artist
    - Keble College Library, University of Oxford, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kensington Grammar School, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kensington School, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kent School Library, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kenyon College, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - King Edward VI Grammar School, Birmingham, England, UK, undated; 3 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - King James Grammar School, Huddersfield, Yorkshire, England, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kings College Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, undated; 7 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kings College Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
      W. S., artist
    - Kings College School Library, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - King's School Library, undated; 2 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kings School Rochester Cathedral, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - K. K. Universitatis-Bibliothek Wien, Vienna, Austria, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Knox College Library, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Ruth Sauders, artist
    - Knox College, Galesburg, IL, undated; 1; note (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Knox College Library, undated; 4 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Knox College, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Tiffany & Co., artist
    - Koenigsberg University Library, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kollegium Studenten Library, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Doerig, artist
    - Kondakovianum Seminarium, Prague, Czech Republic, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Koniglichen Universitatis Munich, Germany, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Konigsberg College, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kremsmunster Monastery Library, Kremsmunster, Austria, 1893 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      G. Otto, artist
    - Kungl. Krigsskolan, Sweden, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - L – R (Box 3, Folder 18-25)
    - Lady Holles's Middle School, Hackney, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lafayette College Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lafayette Junior High School, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lake Erie College, Painesville, OH, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Mrs. Hartley Anderson (of Mitchell, SD), artist
    - Lake Erie College, Painesville, OH, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Collegii Lacus Eriensis, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lake Forest University, Illinois, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lakewood High School, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lancashire Independent College, Manchester, England, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lathom Park Schools, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Latymer Upper School, Hammersmith, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
      E. F. J. H, T. & H. Ltd, artist
    - Lawrence College, Samuel Appleton Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Leavenworth High School, Leavenworth, KA, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Leland Stanford Jr. University, Stanford, CA, undated; 3 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Edwin Howland Blashfield, artist
    - Lewis Institute, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lewisham Grammar School, City of London, England, UK, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Leys School, Cambridge, England, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Libreria di Cappuccini di Cremona, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Libreria Provana di Collegno, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Library of the Convents F.F. Minorum S. Francisci & S. Maria in Augia, Lucerne, c. 1711 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Liceo Paregg.to di Biella, 1929; 2 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      F. Carandini, artist
    - Lime Place Academy, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Limerick Cathedral Grammar School, Limerick, Ireland, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lincoln High School, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lincoln School, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
      M. F. D., artist
    - Lincolnwood School, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Lucy Fitch Perkins, artist
    - Lisboa Instituto Camara Pestana, Portugal, undated; 3 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Liverpool University College, Liverpool, England, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Livorno Accademia Navale, Livorno, Italy, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - London College of Divinity, London, England, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lookout Mountain Educational Institutions, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Loomis Institute Library, Prep. School, Windsor, CT, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Loretto Abbey, Convent Boarding School, Rathfarnham, Ireland, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Marlow Brothers, artist
    - Loretto Convent, Australia, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Loretto Convent, County Cork, Ireland, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
      John Lindsey, artist
    - Los Angeles University of International Relations, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Loughall School Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lucca, undated; 7 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Luiz de Cameos College, Leiria, Portugal, undated; 5 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Lund Universitets, Sweden, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Luther College, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Macclesfelde School, 1790 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Madras Classical School, Bath, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Hollway, artist
    - Madras Classical School, Bath, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Magdalen College, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Magdalen College, Cantabr., undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Magdalen College, University of Cambridge, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Magdalen College, University of Oxford, undated; 6 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Malta Protestant College, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Manchester College Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Manuelium Seminarium Argentinense, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Henri Bacher, artist
    - Marietta College Library, Marietta, OH, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Marine Academy, 1894 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Marischal College, University of Aberdeen, Scotland, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Marlborough College House Library, Wiltshire, England, UK, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Marlborough College, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Marlborough College Adderley Library, undated; 5 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Mary C. Wheeler School, Providence, RI, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Mary C. Wheeler Alumnae Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Edith Barry, artist
    - Mason School, Newton Centre, MA, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Massachusetts Agricultural College, University of Massachusetts, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, 1909; 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Bertha E. Saltmarsh, artist
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, 1919; 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      H.W.G, artist
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, 1909; 5 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Massachusetts School of Art, MIT, Cambridge, MA, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Massachusetts State College, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Massachusetts State Normal School, Worcester, MA, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Massillon School Library, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Maynooth College, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
      H. Fitzpatrick, artist
    - McGaw Institute, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - McGill University Library, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, undated; 9 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Meadville Theological School, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Mechanics Institute (now Rochester Institute of Technology), undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Jack Sullivan, artist
    - Medill School of Journalism, Northwestern University, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Carl S. Junge, artist
    - Meisjes Lyceum, Utrecht, Netherlands, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Nan van Leeuwen, artist
    - Melbourne University, Australia, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Mercers' School, London, England, UK, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Wills Scrip, artist
    - Mercersburg Academy, Mercersburg, PA, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Messina Scuola Industriale, Italy, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Messina Bibl. Universitaria, Italy, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Methodist General Biblical Institute, Concord, NH, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Metz Academie, France, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Metz Centre de Readaptation de Plappeville, France, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
      A. Haefeli, artist
    - Michigan State College, Michigan State University, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Michigan State College of Agriculture and Applied Science, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Lee Laurie, artist
    - Michigan State Univeristy, 1959; 1; bookplate (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Agnes Tait, artist
    - Middlebury College, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      W. M. Aikman, artist
    - Middle Class School, Derby, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Middlesex School, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Milano Monasterio e Collegio di S. Ambrogio Maggiore, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Millbrook School, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
      G. R., artist
    - Mill Hill School Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Mills College, undated; 3 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Miss Howe and Miss Marot's School, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Missieactie Studenten Kaatsheuvel, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Missouri Valley College, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Mommsen Gymnasium, Leipzig, Germany, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Monasterii de Fare, Munich, Germany, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Monasterio d' Escala Dei, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Monastery of Oberzell-on-Main, Germany, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Monastery of Ratisbon, Regensburg, Bavaria, Germany, 1750 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      I. A. Fridrich, artist
    - Monastir de Montserrat, Spain, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Triado, artist
    - Mora Folkhogskola, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Mount Holyoke College, South Hadley, MA, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Mr. Clarke's, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Mr. Fraser's School, Bath, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
      W. I. Kinson, artist
    - Mr. Oliphant's School, Edinburgh, Scotland, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Mr. Pasley's School, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Mrs. Lafarelles Boarding School, Dublin, Ireland, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Munchen Malschule, Munchen, Germany, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Newbury Literary & Scientific Institution, Brikshire, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - New College Oxford, University of Oxford, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
      I. White, artist
    - New Hampshire College of Agriculture and Mechanical Arts, NH, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Newnham College, Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Newton Theological Institution, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - New York Academy of Medicine, NY, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      George Wharton Edwards, artist
    - New York Training School for Deaconesses, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Nizza Accademia dei Neghittosi, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Narrkopings Triwial Scholas, Sweden, 1827 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      O. Levin, artist
    - Nottingham High School, Nottingham, England, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - North High School, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
      M. M., artist
    - North Walsham School, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Northwestern University Library, Illinois, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Northwestern University, Illinois, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Mrs. Frank L. Richardson, artist
    - Oberlin College, Ohio, undated; 3 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Ohio State University, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Okeham Gubern Scholar et Hospiciorum, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Old Harleybury School, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - O'Shaw College, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Owens College (now University of Manchester), UK, undated; 4 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Pacific School of Religion, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Thacher Nelson, artist
    - Palaentological Research Institution, Ithaca, NY, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Amaliesa Caster, artist
    - Pavia, Bibliotheca della Universita, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Peabody Institute, Baltimore, MD, undated; 3 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Peabody Institute, Danvers, MA, undated; 3 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Peabody School, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Wharton, artist
    - People's University, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      L. t. R., artist
    - Pembroke College, University of Cambridge, UK, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Pembroke Hall, later Pembroke College, University of Cambridge, 1700 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Pennsylvania State College, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Peterhouse College, University of Cambridge, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Coll. Div. Pet., undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Coll. Div. Pet., undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Roe, artist
    - Philadelphia Medical College, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Phillips Academy, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Pisa. Bibliotheca del Seminario, Pisa, Italy, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Polytechnic Elementary School, Pasadena, CA, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Pomona College Library, Claremont, CA, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Pomona College, Claremont, CA, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      R.Saunders, artist
    - Poznan University, Poland, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Brouceski, artist
    - Pratt Institute, Brooklyn, NY, undated; 3 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Pratt Institute, Brooklyn, NY, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      E. H. New, artist
    - Pratt Institute Free Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Presbyterian Church College, London, England, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Presbyterian College of England, undated; 4 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Presentation Sisters Pension, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
      H & I Vanderpoorten, Gand., artist
    - Princely Institute Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Princeton University, undated; 8 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Princeton University, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Probyt. Convent of Students Halle in Saale, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Protestant Episcopal Theological School, MA, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Pyman Institute, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Purdue University, Indiana, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Purdue University, Indiana, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Betty Lark, artist
    - Pyman Institute, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Queen Elizabeth Grammar School, Wakefield, England, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Queens College Cambridge, University of Cambridge, UK, 1700; 3 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Queens College Cork (now University College, Cork), undated; 3 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Queens College Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Queens College London, London, England, UK, undated; 4 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      T. Moring, artist
    - Queens College Oxford, University of Oxford, UK, undated; 7 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Queens University Medical Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Radcliffe College Library, undated; 12 items (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Radcliffe College, Oxford, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
      Charles R. Capon, artist
    - Radcliffe College, Oxford, undated; 3 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      J. Gibbs, artist
    - Radcliffe Observatory, Oxford, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Raglan House School, Hadlow, Brighton, England, K, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rasbiologicka Institutet, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      Johan Geksell, artist
    - Reading School, Reading, England, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Real Academia de Ciencias, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Reale Academia delle Scienze di Torino, undated; 2 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Reale Collegio delle Provincie Torino, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Regiae Academiae Pictor Sculptor, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Regia Scuola Tipographica e di Arti Affini di Torino, undated; 3 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Regiae Universitatis, Budapest, Hungary, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
      H. Dolos, artist
    - Regio Liceo Cavour, Torino, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rmensi University H. Raussen Medical Library, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Repton School, Derby, England, UK, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rev. Mr. Lee's School, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
      P. Butler, artist
    - Rev. Mr. Weldon's School, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rhodes University College, South Africa, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rhode Island State College, Providence, RI, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
      J. E., artist
    - Rhode Island School of Design, Procidence, RI, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - R. K. Universiteit Te Nijmegen, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 25)